Truth be told
The Post is a drama, history film directed by Steven Spielberg.
A cover-up that spanned four U.S.
Presidents pushed the country's first female newspaper publisher and a hard-driving
editor to join an unprecedented battle between journalist and government.
Inspired by true events.
Kay Graham, played by Meryl Streep.
Ben Bradlee, played by Tom Hanks.
Tony Bradlee, played by Sarah Paulson.
Ben Bagdikian, played by Bob Odenkirk.
Fritz Beebe, played by Tracy Letts.
Arthur Parsons, played by Bradley Whitford.
The Post is a 2017 American political thriller film about The
Washington Post and the publication of the Pentagon Papers.
It was directed and produced by Steven Spielberg, and
written by Liz Hannah and Josh Singer.
It stars Meryl Streep as Katharine Graham, the publisher of the Washington Post, and Tom Hanks as Ben Bradlee, the longtime executive editor of The Washington Post, with
Sarah Paulson, Bob Odenkirk, Tracy Letts, Bradley Whitford, David Cross, Bruce Greenwood, Carrie Coon, Alison Brie, and Matthew Rhys in supporting roles.
Set in 1971, The Post depicts the true story of attempts by journalists at The Washington Post to publish the infamous Pentagon Papers, a set of classified
documents regarding the 20-year involvement of the United States government in the Vietnam War and earlier in French Indochina back to the 1940s.
Principal photography began in New York City in
May 2017 and wrapped in July 2017.
The film premiered at the Newseum in Washington, D.C., on December 14, 2017, and went into
limited release in the United States by 20th Century Fox on December 22, 2017.
It entered wide release on January 12, 2018, and grossed $179 million worldwide.
The film received positive reviews; critics praised Spielberg's direction, the performances (particularly Streep, Hanks, and
Odenkirk) and the film's references and allusions to the presidencies of Richard Nixon and then-incumbent Donald Trump.
The Post was chosen by the National Board of Review as the best film of 2017 and was named as one
of the top 10 films of the year by Time magazine and the American Film Institute.
The Post was nominated for Best Picture and Best Actress (for Streep) at the 90th Academy Awards, and received six nominations at the 75th Golden Globe Awards: Best
Motion Picture – Drama, Best Director, Best Actress – Drama (for Streep), Best Actor – Drama (for Hanks), Best Screenplay, and Best Original Score.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, newspaper,
journalist, washington dc, usa, politics.
The tone is emotional.